Wilton Historical Society Wilton Historical Information Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- 3. Miscellaneous (by topic)
  - Business and industry
    - Buckhout, Peter, 1783-1806, undated; Peter Buckhout was a merchant in Wilton. (Cabinet 4, Folder 346)
    - Business list, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ab)
    - Businesses - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137a)
    - Buttery Mill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 380b)
    - Cannondale Bicycle Corporation, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137bb)
    - Cider Mill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 381a)
    - Cole & Nichols Carriage Factory / Lockwood Wire Mill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 381b)
    - Constant Comment Tea, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137c)
    - Cook’s Auto Sales, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ca)
    - D. & J. Lockwood, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137caa)
    - Disbrow Motel, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 410b)
    - Elmer’s Town Line Liquors, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137cb)
    - Feeley, Marc - “An American Success Story”, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 322c)
    - Finch Mill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 390c)
    - Gateway Shopping Center, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 347a)
    - Georgetown Mills, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 382)
    - Gilbert & Bennett Wire Factory, undated; See also Book 338.4767182. (Cabinet 4, Folder 322b)
    - Goetjen Moving & Storage, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137d)
    - Gregory Mill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 384)
    - Hatters, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 324)
    - Honey Hill Forge, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 287, 325)
    - Industries - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 321)
    - Inland Wetlands Commission, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 331a)
    - Interracial Summer Camp, 1968 (Cabinet 4, Folder 331aa)
    - Keeler’s store, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 347b)
    - Landfill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 332)
    - Loudon Fixtures (G. Evans Hubbard), undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ea)
    - Maps, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 335)
    - Marvin Tavern, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 337)
    - Mather Street Lands, 1997-1998 (Cabinet 4, Folder 338)
    - Merchant questionnaire, 1969; This is a League of Women Voters questionnaire. (Cabinet 4, Folder 348)
    - Merchants - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 340)
    - Milestone Garage, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ebb)
    - Mills - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 380)
    - Mining and mines, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 391)
    - Minks-to-Sinks sales, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 392)
    - Motels and tourist cabins - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 410c)
    - Norwalk River Watershed Mills, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 388)
    - Olmstead, E. G., undated; E. G. Olmstead was a merchant in Wilton. (Cabinet 4, Folder 353)
    - Orem’s Dairy and Diner, undated; See also WHI, Recreation, Wilton Baseball. (Cabinet 4, Folder 137eb)
    - Pedersen Golf Clubs & Equipment, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ec)
    - Perkin-Elmer Corporation, undated; See also OH. (Cabinet 4, Folder 137f)
    - Real estate, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137fb)
    - Richardson-Vicks, Inc., undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 137fc)
    - Samuel Middlebrook store, 1807-1808 (Cabinet 4, Folder 350)
    - Satinet, Taylor - Glenburg Mill / Old Stone Mill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 390b)
    - Scott, Samuel, 1822-1862; Samuel Scott was a merchant in Wilton. (Cabinet 4, Folder 355)
    - Selleck, James & Sons, 1802-1822 (Cabinet 4, Folder 357)
    - Shirt makers (Olmstead and Sturges), undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ff)
    - Shoemaking, undated; See also 1850 census. (Cabinet 4, Folder 137fff)
    - Silvermine Forge & Mills, undated; See also WHI, Silvermine Mills. (Cabinet 4, Folder 327)
    - Smith, Thomas Herbert mill / Millstone Road, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 390d)
    - Starling / Sterling store, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 358)
    - Stills and breweries, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 330)
    - Stores in Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 493)
    - Taverns and tea rooms, undated; See also WHI, Marvin Tavern and Diary #6, 1714-1977. (Cabinet 4, Folder 500a)
    - Turnover Shop, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137g)
    - Ulack Upholstery & Fabric Store, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ga)
    - Undertakers, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ha)
    - Van Heiningen / Evergreen Nursery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137hb)
    - Village Market, undated; See also WHI, Personalities, Ralph Piersall. (Cabinet 4, Folder 360)
    - Village Market, undated; See also WHI, Merchants. (Cabinet 4, Folder 137hc)
    - Village Market purchase documents, Piersall from Hubbard, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 361)
    - Wilton Arms, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 685)
    - Wilton Bank, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ib)
    - Wilton Electric, undated; Includes notes by G. Evans Hubbard. (Cabinet 4, Folder 137iaa)
    - Wilton Motors, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137jb)
    - Wilton Pharmacy, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ja)
    - Young’s Nurseries, undated; See also GEN, Young. (Cabinet 4, Folder 137ia)
  - Celebrations and observances
    - Arbor Day, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 139d)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Bandshell, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 140c)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Bicentennial Ball, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 140b)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Bicentennial Medal, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 141a)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Committee activities, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 140a)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Committee meeting minutes, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 140e)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 140d)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Newspaper articles, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 140f)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Publications, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 141b)
    - Bicentennial, 1776-1976 - Report, 1975-1977 (Cabinet 4, Folder 140g)
    - Celebrations and observances - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 149d)
    - Christmas activities, undated; Includes crèche history. (Cabinet 4, Folder 143a)
    - Community Observance of September 11, 2001 (Cabinet 4, Folder 143b)
    - Easter, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 143c)
    - Fourth of July, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 144a)
    - Fourth of July - Nod Hill parades, undated; Includes DVDs. (Cabinet 4, Folder 144b)
    - George Washington Bicentennial, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 145)
    - Memorial Day, undated; See also MC 11 for newspaper supplements, See also Videos 394.262 (Cabinet 4, Folder 146)
    - Tercentenary - Correspondence and finances, 1935 (Cabinet 4, Folder 148)
    - Tercentenary - Program, 1935 (Cabinet 4, Folder 149a)
    - Thanksgiving, undated; See also OH tape no. 19. (Cabinet 4, Folder 149b)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Banners and flags (Cabinet 4, Folder 142a)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Calendar (Cabinet 4, Folder 142b)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Coloring book (Cabinet 4, Folder 142ba)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Committee (Cabinet 4, Folder 142c)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Correspondence (Cabinet 4, Folder 142ca)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Finances (Cabinet 4, Folder 142cb)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Founders’ Day (Cabinet 4, Folder 142d)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - HMS Pinafore (Cabinet 4, Folder 142da)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - House Tour and Flower Show (Cabinet 4, Folder 142db)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Marketing (Cabinet 4, Folder 142e)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Minutes and notes (Cabinet 4, Folder 142eb)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Miscellaneous activities (Cabinet 4, Folder 142aa)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Open space events (Cabinet 4, Folder 142ee)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Post Office cancellation (Cabinet 4, Folder 142ef)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Proclamations and letters (Cabinet 4, Folder 142eg)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Publicity (Cabinet 4, Folder 142f)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Tribute to America, Relates to video of a musical program. See Books 920.07469 Tepper for transcripts. (Cabinet 4, Folder 142fa)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Tribute to America - Miscellaneous (Cabinet 4, Folder 142gb)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Tribute to America correspondence (Cabinet 4, Folder 142ga)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Tribute to America interview information (Cabinet 4, Folder 142gc)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Tribute to America video (Cabinet 4, Folder 142gd)
    - Town Bicentennial, 1802-2002 - Wilton School Activities, See also PHO, Bicentennial. (Cabinet 4, Folder 142h)
    - Veteran's Day, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 149c)
  - Cemeteries and churches
    - Bald Hill Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 151a)
    - Bald Hill Methodist Church - Catechism, correspondence, and notes, 1820-1887 (Cabinet 4, Folder 190)
    - Bald Hill Methodist Church - History, undated; See also Scrapbook 61. (Cabinet 4, Folder 191)
    - Baptist Church, Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 162)
    - Beers Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 151ba)
    - Belden Hill Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 151b)
    - Cemeteries - Agreement with Wilton Historical Society, 1997 (Cabinet 4, Folder 151ad)
    - Cemeteries - Computerized lists, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 151ac)
    - Cemeteries - Maps of plots, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 151ab)
    - Cemeteries - Miscellaneous, undated; See also Books 363.75 Cemetery. (Cabinet 4, Folder 150)
    - Cemeteries - Notes of Walter Bassett, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 151aa)
    - Chicken Street Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 151c)
    - Christian Science Church, Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 163aa)
    - Church Records - Connecticut State Library, 1970 (Cabinet 4, Folder 163b)
    - Churches - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 160)
    - Comstock Cemetery, undated; Includes notes by David Hermon Van Hoosear. (Cabinet 4, Folder 152b)
    - Comstock Cemetery, North Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 152a)
    - DeForest Cemetery, undated; See also PHO. (Cabinet 4, Folder 152c)
    - First Burial Ground, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 153a)
    - First Meeting House - Historical marker, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 168bb)
    - Georgetown Cemetery (Batterson), undated; Burials date from 1754 to 1846. (Cabinet 4, Folder 153b)
    - Georgetown churches, undated; Includes Sacred Heart Church, Georgetown Bible, Gilbert Memorial, Bethlehem Lutheran Church, and Old Congregational Church. (Cabinet 4, Folder 184b)
    - Georgetown Methodist Church, 1790-1930 (Cabinet 4, Folder 192)
    - Hillside Cemetery, undated; File 153d includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's notes. Burials date from 1818 through 1936. (Cabinet 4, Folder 153c, 153d)
    - Hillside Cemetery, undated; Includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's index. (Cabinet 4, Folder 153d)
    - Hope Church, circa 1970s (Cabinet 4, Folder 185)
    - Hoyt Cemetery and Scott-Davis Cemetery, undated; Burials at Hoyt Cemetery date from 1829 to 1859. Burials at Scott-Davis date from 1842 through 1908. (Cabinet 4, Folder 156a)
    - Huckleberry Hill Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 153e)
    - Hurlbutt Methodist Church, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 193)
    - Kent Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 154a)
    - Kent Methodist Church, South Wilton, 1888 (Cabinet 4, Folder 194)
    - Methodist churches - General information, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 189)
    - Morgan Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 154ba)
    - Nod Hill Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 154bb)
    - Olmstead Hill Cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 154c)
    - Our Lady of Fatima Church, Wilton, undated; See also Pamphlet Box, “Our Lady of Fatima.” (Cabinet 4, Folder 163a)
    - Presbyterian Church, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 188)
    - Quakers, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 196)
    - Ruscoe Cemetery, undated; See also Books 363.75 Ceretani. (Cabinet 4, Folder 154d)
    - Sharp Hill Cemetery, undated; Burials date from 1755 through 1950. File 157b includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's notes. (Cabinet 4, Folder 157a, 157b)
    - Silver Spring / Hoyt Cemetery, undated; Burials date from 1829 through 1859. (Cabinet 4, Folder 156b)
    - Society of Friends, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 197)
    - Spruce Bank (Slave Cemetery), undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 157c)
    - St. Matthew's Cemetery, undated; File 155b includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's notes. See also MAN. (Cabinet 4, Folder 155a, 155b, 155ab)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, Wilton, 1802; See also Pamphlet Box, “St. Matthew’s Episcopal Church" (Cabinet *, Folder *)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, Wilton - Building and land, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 180)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, Wilton - Canterbury Market, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 181)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, Wilton - History, undated; See also Scrapbook 57 and Books 283.7469. (Cabinet 4, Folder 182a, 182aa)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, Wilton - History by David Hermon Van Hoosear, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 182b)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, Wilton - Members and ministers, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 183)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, Wilton - Programs, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 184a)
    - Tombstones, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 158a)
    - United Covenant Church, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 197b)
    - Unnamed cemetery, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 158b)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Abstracts from society records, 1726-1805; Abstracts are by G. Evans Hubbard. (Cabinet 4, Folder 168d)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Annual reports and newsletters, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 164a)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Baptisms list, 1737-1800 (Cabinet 4, Folder 164b)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Benevolent Society, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 164c)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Birth records, 1700-1800 (Cabinet 4, Folder 165)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Building, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 166)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Celebrations and programs, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 167a)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Dana property, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 167b)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - General history, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 168a)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Ladies Home Missionary Society - Members and seating, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 169)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Ladies Home Missionary Society - Ministers, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 170)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Ladies Home Missionary Society - Parsonages, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 171a)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Ladies Home Missionary Society - Wilton Society, undated; See also Books 285.87469. (Cabinet 4, Folder 172)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Ladies Home Missionary Society - Yankee Fair, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 171b)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Petitions, 1726; See also MAN, Town Records. (Cabinet 4, Folder 168c)
    - Zion's Hill Cemetery - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 158c)
    - Zion's Hill Cemetery - Plot burials, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 158d)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - 150th Anniversary, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195a)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Administrative Board minutes, 1972-1992 (Cabinet 4, Folder 195o)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Annual reports, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195b)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Budget reports, 1971-1993 (Cabinet 4, Folder 195j)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Building and land, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195c)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Charge Conference minutes, 1989-1993 (Cabinet 4, Folder 195p)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Christian education / Sunday school, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195d)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Church Conference reports, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195e)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Committee reports, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195f)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Council of Missions minutes, 1985-1991 (Cabinet 4, Folder 195q)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Dedication / rededication, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195g)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Directory, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195h)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Ecumenical group, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195i)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Finances, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195j)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Future Task Force, 1991 (Cabinet 4, Folder 195l)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - General information, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195lf)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - History, undated; File 195la covers the years 1844-1897. File 195lb covers the years 1898-1919. File 195lc covers the years 1920-1924. File 195ld covers the years 1925-1935. File 195le covers the years 1936 onward. (Cabinet 4, Folder 195la)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Members, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195m)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Ministers, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195n)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Newsletters, 1986-1993; File 195rb contains the 1992 newsletter. File 195rc contains the 1993 newsletter. (Cabinet 4, Folder 195ra, 195rb, 195rc)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Other anniversaries, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195ab)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Parsonage, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195s)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Special Events, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195t)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Surveys and minister’s audit, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 195u)
    - Zion's Hill Methodist Church - Treasurer’s reports, 1972-1993 (Cabinet 4, Folder 195k)
  - Civic and social organizations
    - Adopt A Spot, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 203bb)
    - American Legion, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 200, 201)
    - American Legion Post 86 - Records, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 102bbb)
    - Boy Scouts of America, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 203a, 479)
    - Camden Clothing Drive, undated; See also WHI, Civic Organizations, Friends of Children. (Cabinet 4, Folder 137k)
    - Civic League, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 203c)
    - Civic organizations and charities - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 203b)
    - Comstock Community Center, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 227g)
    - Encore Club, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 203d)
    - Exchange Club, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 203e)
    - Friends of Children, Clothing Drive and Camden Fund, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 204b)
    - Georgetown - Girl Scouts, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 289e)
    - Junior Red Cross, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 206)
    - Kiwanis, undated; See also Kiwanis Archives in Cabinet Brown 17, Scrapbook #40, and 12 volumes on Black Bookshelf 20. (Cabinet 4, Folder 207)
    - Masons, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 211)
    - Mid-Fairfield Child Guidance Center, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 213)
    - Odd Fellows, 1842-1895 (Cabinet 4, Folder 215)
    - Red Cross, 1945 (Cabinet 4, Folder 217)
    - Rotary Club of Wilton, undated; See also archives on Black Bookshelf 20. (Cabinet 4, Folder 219)
    - Silverspring Country Club, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 482)
    - Sons of the American Revolution (SAR), undated; See also MAP TUBE #3. (Cabinet 4, Folder 489)
    - Stay at Home in Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 491)
    - Teen / Youth Center Benefit Tape, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 503)
    - Wilton Education Foundation, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 221)
    - Wilton Homemakers, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 225a)
    - Wilton Improvement Society, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 225b)
    - Wilton Residential Association, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 226a)
    - Wilton Safe Rides, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 226b)
    - Wilton Taxpayers Association, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 753aaa)
    - Wilton Youth Action, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 227c)
    - Women's Republican Club of Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 227d)
    - YMCA, undated; Includes Distinguished Citizen Awards. (Cabinet 4, Folder 227e)
    - Young Men's Debating Club, 1908 (Cabinet 4, Folder 227f)
  - Entertainment, recreation, and sports
    - Actors and actresses, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 507)
    - Cannon Men’s Chorus - Correspondence, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 410d)
    - Cannon Men’s Chorus - Minutes, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 410f)
    - Cannon Men’s Chorus - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 410e)
    - Cannon Men’s Chorus - Music, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 410g)
    - Circus, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 198)
    - Comstock Fife & Drum Corps, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 411a)
    - Entertainment, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 270)
    - Golf, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470d)
    - Hobbies, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 319ab)
    - Horse riding and racing / Wilton Pony Club, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470e)
    - Lacrosse history, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470ea)
    - Nutmeg Music Theater, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 412a)
    - Parent-Teacher Association Choral Club, undated; See also Scrapbook 48 and PTA Choral Club program, 1947 (Cabinet 4, Folder 411b)
    - Parent-Teacher Association Choral Club - Scrapbook pages, undated; Includes original pages from Scrapbook 48. See also OH, tape 30. (Cabinet 4, Folder 412b)
    - Recreational programs, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470f)
    - Report on Recreation Study, 1965; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 470g)
    - Society of the No Friends of Music, undated; See also MAN, Unpublished Manuscripts. The Annals of the Society of the No Friends of Music is stored in the library basement. (Cabinet 4, Folder 412c)
    - Sports, 1898-1956 (Cabinet 4, Folder 490)
    - Sports and recreation - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470c)
    - "Study to Identify and Evaluate Recreational Needs of Wilton's Youth", 1976 (Cabinet 4, Folder 470h)
    - Theater-in-the-Woods, 1931-1941 (Cabinet 4, Folder 512)
    - Wilton Athletic Club, 1975 (Cabinet 4, Folder 470hb)
    - Wilton baseball, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470i)
    - Wilton Choral Club, 1922-1960 (Cabinet 4, Folder 510, 511)
    - Wilton Family Recreation Activities Center (WFRAC), 2000 (Cabinet 4, Folder 470j)
    - Wilton Rod and Gun Club, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470k)
    - Wilton Singers, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 412d)
    - World’s Fair, New York, 1939 (Cabinet 4, Folder 275a)
  - Government and services
    - Bald Hill Post Office, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 460b)
    - Cannondale Post Office, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 461)
    - Census - Centenarians, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 159e)
    - Census - List of Wilton heads of households, 1810-1900; File 159b covers 1810. File 159c covers 1900. (Cabinet 4, Folder 159b, 159c)
    - Census - List of Wilton residents, 1958; See also MC 8 and MAP TUBE #12. (Cabinet 4, Folder 159d)
    - Census - Miscellaneous, 1802-1990; File 159a covers the years 1802-1850. File 159ab covers the year 1990. See also The Barbour Collection of Connecticut Town Vital Records (929.3 Barbour). (Cabinet 4, Folder 159a, 159ab)
    - Census of Wilton, undated; See also MICROFILMS. (Cabinet 4, Folder 290)
    - Citizens' committees, railroad, and telephone, 1912-1913 (Cabinet 4, Folder 551)
    - Democrats, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 455)
    - Elections, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 456)
    - Fire Department - 50th Year of Service Dinner, and other events, 1978 (Cabinet 4, Folder 286)
    - Fire Department - By-laws, recommendations, 1972 (Cabinet 4, Folder 281)
    - Fire Department - Minstrel shows, 1934-1945 (Cabinet 4, Folder 283, 284a)
    - Fire department - Miscellaneous, 1934-1945 (Cabinet 4, Folder 280a)
    - Fire Department - Shoff property, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 284b)
    - Georgetown Fire Department, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 280b)
    - Georgetown Post Office, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 462)
    - Housing - Human services, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 319e)
    - Housing - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 319ad)
    - Housing - Ogden House - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 424a)